http://ccmostwanted.com/privacy-policy-2

Internet Safety
Internet Shopping GuidelinesInternet PrivacyIdentity TheftNetiquetteWorld Credit Reporting AgenciesDigital DivideFamily Internet SafetySeniors Internet Safety
Computer Security
Network SecurityEncryptionFirewallsIntrusion DetectionSecurity Tradeshows Events and SeminarsElectronics Recycling and DisposalDownloadsComputer Infectors & VirusesInfectious Email Attachments
Spyware
SPAM
Cybercrime
Internet Scams and Hoaxes
ScamsInternet HoaxesNigerian ScamsConsumer FraudInvestment FraudReport Stolen ComputerCyberterrorismCyberstalkingComputer HackingReport Cybercrime in the USAReport Cybercrime CanadaReport Cybercrime WorldwideComputer Crime Investigators
Global Computer Crime Task Forces
USA Computer Crime Task ForcesGlobal Law Enforcement PrecinctsUSA County Sheriff OfficesCrime Victims
Most Wanted
FBI 10 Most WantedMost Wanted TerroristsMost Wanted HijackersMost Wanted Past Cyber Fugitives
Cyber Law
USA Cyber Law
International Cyber LawAttorney ReferenceLaw Enforcement ReferencesGlobal Internet Law AttorneysUSA Internet Law AttorneysComputer Forensic SpecialistsExpert Witnesses
Kids
Internet Safety for Kids
Netiquette for KidsEmail for KidsInternet PrivacyKids Computer Hacking
Computer Infectors & Viruses
Online Scams Hoaxes and FraudNaughty People OnlineReport Cyber BullyingInteractive Internet Safety WebsitesSchoolwork WebsitesFind HelpReferences
ContactResources
Resource Pages
Fun WebsitesParents ResourcesTeenagersTeachers Resources
Privacy Policycyber2013-07-26T14:39:12+00:00
Privacy Policy – www.ccmostwanted.coPrivacy Policy for www.ccmostwanted.com
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at cc@ccmostwanted.com.
At www.ccmostwanted.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ccmostwanted.com and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, www.ccmostwanted.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.ccmostwanted.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.ccmostwanted.com.
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to www.ccmostwanted.com and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.ccmostwanted.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.ccmostwanted.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.ccmostwanted.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Popular
Recent
Two Interesting German Desicions On The Internet Law
July 21st, 2013
Cyber attacks will cause real world harm in next seven years
September 26th, 2013
The Legal Community has Become Part of the Cyber Security Equation, “But Don’t Run Before You Can Walk,” says Global Digital Forensics Founder
August 23rd, 2013
WordPress vulnerability leaves millions of servers open to hacks
May 7th, 2015
Can Online Gambling Ever Be Fully Safe?
May 26th, 2014
Cyber attacks will cause real world harm in next seven years
September 26th, 2013
Cyber attacks to escalate over next decade
September 26th, 2013
Kaspersky Lab Uncovers New Cyber Hit-n-Run Operation Called ‘Icefog’
September 26th, 2013
Should Madware Be Considered An Internet Security Threat?
September 10th, 2013
Kids, dont share too much online!
August 31st, 2013
Snowden Leak Reveals NSA conducted 231 Offensive Cyber Operations in 2011
August 31st, 2013
Back-to-School 101: Internet safety
August 31st, 2013
REPORT: ‘Brilliant’ Snowden Digitally Impersonated NSA Officials
August 30th, 2013
Banks and Utilities Possible Targets from Wave of Syrian Cyber Attacks
August 29th, 2013
Syrian Electronic Army claim ‘take over’ of Twitter and New York Times in Cyber Attacks
August 28th, 2013
Warning of Major Cyber Event by Outgoing US Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano
The Legal Community has Become Part of the Cyber Security Equation, “But Don’t Run Before You Can Walk,” says Global Digital Forensics Founder
Larry Olszewski says:
I keep recieveing an email and I know it's bogus! It's supposedly...
Benjamin says:
MacBook Pro Retina 13" Late 2012
Stolen in Vienna, Austria on 2/13/2014
Serial is...
LaTanya Owens says:
How will this terrorism with cyber attack be stopped?...
Tweet
